<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Case studies on Sample Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Case studies on Sample Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/case-studies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Barchester Healthcare VoC Case Study</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/barchester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/barchester/</guid>
      <description>Company: Barchester Healthcare&#xA;Location: Throughout the UK – 250 care homes and mental health hospitals.&#xA;One of the biggest independent care providers in the UK, Barchester specialises in delivering top quality care.&#xA;{:class=&amp;ldquo;longform-pull-right&amp;rdquo;}We asked Sarah Lander-Scott, Head of Customer Contact &amp;amp; Experience, to describe her experience of measuring and improving Net Promoter Score using real-time feedback from residents, family and friends.&#xA;Tell us about Barchester… We provide care for those who need it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chartboost | Case Studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/chartboost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/chartboost/</guid>
      <description>Company Chartboost Location San Francisco, US Chartboost is a technology company based in San Francisco and their fun loving culture is evident in the playful design of their offices.&#xA;Although their work is about fun &amp;amp; games they&amp;rsquo;re deadly serious about customer service.&#xA;They were already working hard on service, but they felt they could strengthen their business by doing even better, and they wanted to benefit from having customer feedback integrated into their processes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covéa Insurance | Case Studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/covea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/covea/</guid>
      <description>{:style=&amp;lsquo;width: 40%&amp;rsquo;}&#xA;Company Covéa Insurance Location Halifax, UK Covéa Insurance Plc is the UK underwriting business of leading French mutual insurance group Covéa.&#xA;One of the top 75 employers in West Yorkshire and Humber, and the winner of multiple industry awards, they have a longstanding commitment to an effective Voice of the Customer programme.&#xA;They knew that to improve further, they needed a more flexible software platform, and a trusted partner to help with implementation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Wish Coffee | Case Studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/deathwishcoffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/deathwishcoffee/</guid>
      <description>Company Death Wish Coffee Location New York, shipping high-caffeine coffee worldwide. Death Wish Coffee solve the multiple cups problem faced by most coffee drinkers. From their New York base, they ship ultra-high-caffeine coffee to hundreds of thousands of coffee fans worldwide. One cup of Death Wish, and these drinkers never need worry about a second cup, or indeed, sleep for the rest of the week.&#xA;Founded in 2012 and growing rapidly year-on-year, you may have caught their Superbowl commercial in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GBGroup | Case Studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/gbg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/gbg/</guid>
      <description>Company: GBG Location: International presence with customers in over 60 countries. GBG provide global specialist identity data services. When organisations need to prevent fraud, vet their employees, or ensure their customer data is accurate, they turn to GBG to help.&#xA;They’re a young, innovative company, and their rapid growth provides ample opportunity for their team members to grow and develop themselves.&#xA;To make this growth sustainable, they need to keep their existing customers happy, which is why they chose CustomerSure to help run their global VoC Program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Marmalade Insurance improves customer experience [Case Study]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/how-marmalade-insurance-improve-customer-experience-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/how-marmalade-insurance-improve-customer-experience-case-study/</guid>
      <description>Company: Marmalade Insurance&#xA;Location: Peterborough, UK&#xA;Marmalade is a trail-blazing insurance company, dedicated to younger drivers, with a reputation for innovation.&#xA;We asked Jenny Lakin, Customer Insight Manager, to describe her experience of using real-time feedback to measure and improve customer experience.&#xA;Tell us about Marmalade… &amp;ldquo;Marmalade provides innovative and practical insurance solutions exclusively for young drivers between the ages of 17 and 30.&#xA;Our insurance is suitable for learner drivers, qualified drivers, people who own their own cars, those who are sharing or borrowing someone else’s car, drivers looking for annual cover and those looking for short term, flexible options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Optimus improves decision-making with real-time VoC data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/optimus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/optimus/</guid>
      <description>{:height=&amp;lsquo;70&amp;rsquo;}&#xA;Tell us about Optimus Optimus is a tech company based in the property services sector. We provide conveyancing and home surveys via a technology platform connected to a nationwide panel of conveyancers and surveyors. Working alongside our panels, Optimus have a expert service team who ensure the performance of their panels and support the end-to-end home moving process to deliver a high level of service across the customer journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Polypipe learnt to benefit from customer feedback.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/how-polypipe-learnt-to-benefit-from-customer-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/how-polypipe-learnt-to-benefit-from-customer-feedback/</guid>
      <description>Company: Polypipe Building Products&#xA;Location: Doncaster, UK&#xA;Whether it’s for new build or refurbishment projects, Polypipe’s Building Products business recognises the demands of modern construction environments and works across all disciplines to help industry professionals to get the job done.&#xA;We asked Dean Asher, Head of Technical and Customer Services, to tell us about his experience of implementing a customer feedback system.&#xA;Tell us about Polypipe. We manufacture plastic pipes and we supply a wide range of water management and heating solutions that help our construction customers build better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Spark Energy improve their CX [Case Study]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/spark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/spark/</guid>
      <description>Company: Spark Energy Location: Selkirk, Scotland Spark Energy, are an exciting challenger brand in the UK’s energy sector. They’ve supplied energy to over 350,000 people across the country, and continue to grow, now as part of the OVO Energy family, thanks to their focus on service and simplicity.&#xA;Because energy is a competitive market, with razor-thin profit margins, Spark need to be better at service than their competition to retain their customers, and build a steady stream of recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Digital Marketing Institute improves their NPS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/how-the-digital-marketing-institute-improves-net-promoter-score/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/how-the-digital-marketing-institute-improves-net-promoter-score/</guid>
      <description>Company: Digital Marketing Institute Location: Blackrock, Ireland We asked Ellie McHugh, Global Operations Director, to share her experience of customer journey mapping and improving Net Promoter Score.&#xA;Tell us about the Digital Marketing Institute&amp;hellip; The Digital Marketing Institute is the global standard in digital marketing training and certification – providing the skills, confidence and industry know-how to stay relevant in the ever-changing digital world through our Membership.&#xA;{:class=&amp;lsquo;longform-content-image&amp;rsquo;}&#xA;The DMI course content and exams are validated by some of the top change makers in the marketing industry: The Global Industry Advisory Council</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KK Wind Case Study</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/kk-wind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/kk-wind/</guid>
      <description>Company: KK Wind Solutions&#xA;Location: KK Wind Solutions is headquartered in Denmark and operates in eight countries across Europe, Asia, and North America.&#xA;{:class=&amp;ldquo;longform-pull-right&amp;rdquo;}&#xA;Kenneth Damm Hansen is Director – Marketing &amp;amp; Communication. We asked Kenneth to describe his experience of choosing and implementing CustomerSure as the customer experience platform for KK Wind.&#xA;Tell us about KK Wind Solutions Building on more than 40 years of experience, KK Wind Solutions is a strong partner in electro-mechanical systems for wind turbines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiftpage | Case Studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/swiftpage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/swiftpage/</guid>
      <description>Company Swiftpage Location Newcastle, UK, and Scottsdale, AZ Swiftpage is the brand behind Act! – the best-selling Contact &amp;amp; Customer Manager. It&amp;rsquo;s a fun loving, fast-moving, &amp;lsquo;can do&amp;rsquo; culture with people at the core – the people who deliver service and the customers who receive it.&#xA;Faced with the challenge of delivering high quality software and exceptional service to customers around the world, they knew that improving customer satisfaction would drive up contract renewals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking the Philips Customer Feedback Programme International</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/philips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/philips/</guid>
      <description>Philips, a global leader in innovation, is committed to enhancing people’s lives through meaningful products.&#xA;The Philips Sonicare brand, known for its popular dental care products, sought to engage dental professionals, gather valuable feedback, and raise brand awareness within this crucial customer segment across Western Europe and the US.&#xA;This case study takes a closer look at the ongoing partnership Philips has with CustomerSure through our ever-evolving Global Supplier Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tastecard | Case Studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/tastecard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/tastecard/</guid>
      <description>Company: Tastecard Location: Huddersfield, UK Tell us about Tastecard Tastecard is the UK&amp;rsquo;s largest diners&amp;rsquo; club, providing millions of members with 2 for 1 meals or 50% off food at over 6500 restaurants.&#xA;We help to make dining experiences affordable for everyone - and we also help to keep restaurants busy.&#xA;The reason tastecard is so popular is the value of the offer - we try to offer the deepest and most simple discounts to our members, so that they know what to expect every single time they dine out using the card.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBT | Case Studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/ubt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/ubt/</guid>
      <description>Company: UBT Location: International presence in 19 countries. UBT is a business membership group that helps its member companies to prosper through advice, training and collective purchasing power. Customer satisfaction lies at the heart of everything they do.&#xA;An important aspect of UBT culture is contributing to charities and supporting the local community.&#xA;We interviewed Bob Calder, Customer Service Team Leader.&#xA;{:class=&amp;lsquo;longform-content-image&amp;rsquo;}&#xA;Tell us about UBT We&amp;rsquo;re in the business advisory industry.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
